Mr. Big Stuff - Jean Knight
I'm A Little Teapot (Edit) - Larry Groce
Heaven Is One Step Away - Eric Clapton
Come On, Let's Go - Los Lobos
Buzzsaw Attack (Minus Lead Guitar) - Harold Faltermeyer
Wheels on the Bus Opposites Song (Instrumental) - The Kiboomers
Jesu, Joy of Man's Desiring - Cantata No. 147 - Elena Duran
Benny & Joon (Reprise) - Rachel Portman
빙글이가 거꾸로 빙그르르 돌리면 - 스토리텔러 레몽
La-La Means I Love You - The Delfonics
Through the Arbor - Kevin Kern
Who Do You Love - Bo Diddley
빙글이가 거꾸로 빙그르르 돌리면 - 스토리텔러 레몽
Slaughter On 10th Avenue - The Ventures
Because I Loved You - Richard Stoltzman
Perfidia - The Ventures
Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da - Celia Cruz
Por Una Cabeza - Carlos Gardel